jobopenings.net 2002-06-02

# Privacy Policy Statement for JobOpenings.net

This Overall Privacy Statement verifies that The **Job Openings.net** (JO) is in compliance with **PrivacySecure** ® privacy principles and guidelines. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire site, including all other domain names owned by Accounting & Computer Enterprises, Inc.

**PrivacySecure** ® **, Inc.** is a Virginia corporation whose mission is to make a significant contribution to commerce on the Internet by providing a means for users of Internet services to have confidence in the published privacy statements of companies collecting information about users and visitors to their site.  Because this site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed and audited for compliance by **PrivacySecure** ®. When you visit a Web site displaying the **PrivacySecure** ® logo, you can expect to be notified of: 

> 1\. What information The **Job Openings.net** gathers/tracks about you   
>  2\. What The **Job Openings.net** does with the information it gathers/tracks   
>  3\. With whom The **Job Openings.net** shares the information it gathers/tracks 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to The JO Customer Service at [support@jobopenings.net](mailto:support@jobopenings.net). Read Frequently Asked Questions About [Cookies](http://www.centralvirginia.net/ace-lynchburg/Orders/FAQ.htm).

* * *

The **Job Openings.net** **(JO)** has adopted a set of information management guidelines which serve as the basis for our customer and advertiser relationships. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page. 

**1\. What information does The Job Openings.net gather/track about you?**

**JO** requires that job applicants and others supply personal information, including e-mail address, during a "registration" process prior to using some portions of the site and to add a listing to the site. (Some of the personal information we request is voluntary; the word "not required" appears next to these questions.) On occasion, **JO** also collects additional personal information from subscribers in optional contest and survey forms. Demographic information provided by a subscriber may be combined with site usage reports to profile, in aggregate form, users and their preferences in site content and advertising. 

**JO** also logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We do not log IP addresses to track a user's session, nor do we link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. 

**2\. What does The Job Openings.net do with the information it gathers/tracks?**

**JO** may perform statistical analyses of user behavior in order to measure relative consumer interest in the various areas of our site (for service development purposes) and to inform advertisers as to how many consumers have seen their advertising banners. In performance of these statistical analyses, we will disclose information to third parties only in aggregate form. Personal information on individual subscribers will not be provided to any third party except for Job Openings.net sponsors and partners as needed to help applicants in job searches. 

Using the e-mail addresses provided at registration, **JO** periodically sends promotional e-mail to its subscribers about services offered by **JO** and its advertisers. A user can indicate on the subscriber registration form that he or she does not wish to receive e-mail information from **JO** or its advertisers. **JO** may contact a subscriber regarding account status or changes to the subscriber agreement. 

**3\. With whom does The Job Openings.net share the information it gathers/tracks?**

**JO** shares the information it tracks, in aggregate form, with advertisers and other partners. We do not sell or share email addresses with third parties or advertisers except for partners or site sponsors.  **JO** will provide a subscriber a summary of his or her personal information provided at registration upon request. This information will only be sent to the e-mail address on file for the subscriber name associated with it. 

Upon request, **JO** will remove any subscriber or job applicant (and his or her personal information) from our database, or allow any subscriber to "opt out" of further contact (while still allowing access to the site) or change/correct personal information that the subscriber states is erroneous. To obtain an information summary or request a change of information, send e-mail to [Customer Service](mailto:support@jobopenings.net). 

**JO** is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Web sites to which it may link.
